eogn.com 2014-03-30

# Privacy - Eastman's Online Genealogy Newsletter

**Privacy**

I take your privacy very seriously. If you have any questions on my privacy policy that are not addressed below, please contact Dick Eastman. Telephone numbers, email address, FAX numbers, and more are available at <http://blog.eogn.com/eastmans_online_genealogy//contact-us.html>

**E-mail Address**

When you subscribe, your e-mail address is added to the list of subscribers and is only used to send your issues and occasional notices of offers from business partners. Also, about once a year or so, I may send a special notice.

I hate spam so I do not send spam. I will not add your name to anyone's e-mail list without your permission. I will not sell, rent, or otherwise share your e-mail address with anyone else.

You can remove your address from my e-mailing list by following the instructions at the end of every e-mail message I send. Removing your address only takes a second or two and you can do that at any time.

 **Personal Information**

I will never ask you for personal information – your credit card number, for example – except when you place an order. At that time, I will provide a secure (SSL, encrypted) connection and require you to submit only the information needed to complete and fulfill your order. 

A few seconds later, my automated system immediately erases your credit card number. For security reasons, I will never store credit card numbers. Nobody can "hack" into any of my computers to steal your credit card number simply because that information does not exist in my computers.

I will not sell or rent your personal information to anyone, nor share it in any other way, unless required to by a law enforcement agency that takes the proper steps to require it. In other words, I only supply personal information to the authorities after receiving a court order to do so.

 **Copyright and Disclaimer**

All contents of this website are copyright by Dick Eastman. However, unlike most other web sites, you are actually **encouraged** to republish the Standard Edition articles elsewhere, in print or online. You may copy-and-paste articles to email messages, newsgroups, blogs, Facebook, Twitter, Google Plus, other social network sites, or publish them in your society's printed newsletters. You do not need to ask permission. "Just Do It."

You are asked to attribute the original source of the article, however. Details may be found at <http://blog.eogn.com/eastmans_online_genealogy/copyrights-and-other-lega.html>

**Additional Information**

Questions? Please contact Dick Eastman: <http://blog.eogn.com/eastmans_online_genealogy//contact-us.html>

  * Your email address is safe with me. I promise that:

    1. I will never sell, rent, or give away your address to any outside party, ever;
    2. You can click the link at the bottom of any email I send to instantly and securely unsubscribe. Period.

  * April 11th to 14th, 2014 - Annual Guild of One-Name Studies Conference, [Ashford, Kent, United Kingdom](http://www.one-name.org/conf2014_ashford.html)

April 19, 2014 - Tacoma-Pierce County Genealogical Society, [Tacoma, Washington](http://www.rootsweb.ancestry.com/~watpcgs/seminar.html)

April 27, 2014 - Genealogical Society of Washtenaw County, [Michigan](http://washtenawgenealogy.org/)

May 7 to 10, 2014 - National Genealogical Society annual conference, [ Richmond, Virginia](http://conference.ngsgenealogy.org/)

June 6 to 8, 2014 - Southern California Genealogy Jamboree, [ Burbank, California](http://genealogyjamboree.com/)

June 14, 2014 - Middlesex Society of Genealogists, Middlesex County, Massachusetts

10-11 October 2014 - Western Michigan Genealogical Society's Annual Seminar, [ Grand Rapids, Michigan](http://gotancestors.com/)

December 7 to 14, 2014 -Eastern Caribbean Genealogy Cruise - [ Fort Lauderdale, Florida; San Juan, Puerto Rico; Basseterre, St. Kitts and Philipsburg, St. Maarten](http://www.cecruisegroups.com/genealogy-cruise-2014.html)

11 April 2015 - Imperial Polk Genealogical Society Seminar 2015, [ Lakeland, Florida](http://www.ipgs.org/)

* * *

**Dick Eastman LIVE at your event**

Dick Eastman is available for presentations and full-day seminars at genealogy conferences around the world. Dick knows that sitting through a boring speech is painful. Therefore, he keeps things light and humorous, giving presentations that are educational, motivational, and entertaining.

[Contact Dick Eastman](http://blog.eogn.com/eastmans_online_genealogy//contact-us.html) for more information. 

* * *

**Search This Newsletter's Past Articles**
